Playtime is over.
The Boss Baby: Family Business is a animation, comedy,
adventure film directed by Tom McGrath.
The Templeton brothers — Tim and his Boss Baby little bro Ted —
have become adults and drifted away from each other.
But a new boss baby with a cutting-edge approach and a can-do attitude is about
to bring them together again … and inspire a new family business.
Theodore Templeton (voice), played by Alec Baldwin.
Tim Templeton (voice), played by James Marsden.
Tina Templeton (voice), played by Amy Sedaris.
Tabitha Templeton (voice), played by Ariana Greenblatt.
Dr. Armstrong (voice), played by Jeff Goldblum.
Carol Templeton (voice), played by Eva Longoria.
The Boss Baby: Family Business (known in some territories as The Boss Baby 2) is a
2021 American animated comedy film produced by DreamWorks Animation.
Loosely based on the picture books The Boss Baby and The Bossier Baby by Marla Frazee, it is the
second installment in The Boss Baby franchise, and the sequel to The Boss Baby.
The film was directed by Tom McGrath and written by Michael McCullers.
It stars the voices of Amy Sedaris, Ariana Greenblatt, Jeff Goldblum, and Eva Longoria, with Alec Baldwin, Jimmy
Kimmel, and Lisa Kudrow reprising their roles from the first film and James Marsden replacing Tobey Maguire.
The film follows the now-adult Templeton brothers as they are brought back together after Tim's daughter
Tina requests their help for Baby Corp to stop a professor from erasing childhoods worldwide.
Plans for a Boss Baby sequel were announced in May
2017 with McGrath returning to direct.
Animation began at DWA Glendale and some production assets were borrowed from Jellyfish
Pictures, with voice acting being done remotely due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The film was theatrically released in the United States on July 2, 2021, by Universal
Pictures, and was also available on paid tiers of Peacock for 60 days.
The film grossed $146 million against a budget of $82 million.
The film explores themes of baby, boss, sequel, sibling, family.
The tone is lighthearted.